{
  "LevelId": 74,
  "Questions": [
    {
      "id": 756,
      "level_image": 6,
      "answer_text": "CARMAKERS",
      "question": "industry is responsible for manufacturing automobiles, and is comprised of companies that design"
    },
    {
      "id": 757,
      "level_image": 6,
      "answer_text": "BREAKNECK",
      "question": "speed or pace does an activity or movement occur when it is extremely fast and potentially reckless"
    },
    {
      "id": 758,
      "level_image": 6,
      "answer_text": "BEATBOXED",
      "question": "the rhythmic vocal percussion often used to mimic drum sounds"
    },
    {
      "id": 759,
      "level_image": 6,
      "answer_text": "GRAVEWARD",
      "question": "place or area is the final resting site for the deceased, often marked by tombstones"
    },
    {
      "id": 760,
      "level_image": 6,
      "answer_text": "FRANKLINS",
      "question": "the common term used to refer to one hundred-dollar bills in the United States"
    },
    {
      "id": 761,
      "level_image": 6,
      "answer_text": "FLAMBEAUS",
      "question": "torches, especially those used in festive processions or celebrations,"
    },
    {
      "id": 762,
      "level_image": 6,
      "answer_text": "OLEANDERS",
      "question": "toxic flowering shrubs, known for their vibrant and colorful blooms,"
    },
    {
      "id": 763,
      "level_image": 6,
      "answer_text": "FLASHGUNS",
      "question": "photographic equipment produces a brief burst of intense light,"
    },
    {
      "id": 764,
      "level_image": 6,
      "answer_text": "HOOFBEATS",
      "question": "rhythmic sounds do you hear when horses are in motion,"
    },
    {
      "id": 765,
      "level_image": 0,
      "answer_text": "KNOWLEDGE",
      "question": "gain through learning, experience, and understanding"
    }
  ]
}